{
   "QA":[
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-c2",
         "type":"Pair",
         "question":"Lea/der",
         "correctAnswer":"Leader"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-c3",
         "type":"Pair",
         "question":"Tea/cher",
         "correctAnswer":"Teacher"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-c4",
         "type":"Pair",
         "question":"Prin/ci/pal",
         "correctAnswer":"Principal"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-c6",
         "type":"Pair",
         "question":"Coa/ch",
         "correctAnswer":"Coach"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-c7",
         "type":"Pair",
         "question":"Dri/ver",
         "correctAnswer":"Driver"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-c11",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Moni/tor",
        "correctAnswer":"Monitor"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-c12",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Hel/lo",
        "correctAnswer":"Hello"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-c13",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Stu/dent",
        "correctAnswer":"Student"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-c14",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Good/bye",
        "correctAnswer":"Goodbye"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-d1",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Dau/gh/ter",
        "correctAnswer":"Daughter"
     },
     {
        "QID":"p1u2-d2",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Ba/by",
        "correctAnswer":"Baby"
     },
     {
        "QID":"p1u2-d3",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Fam/ily",
        "correctAnswer":"Family"
     },
     {
        "QID":"p1u2-d4",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Un/cle",
        "correctAnswer":"Uncle"
     },
     {
        "QID":"p1u2-d5",
        "type":"Pair",
        "question":"Fa/ther",
        "correctAnswer":"Father"
     },
     {
       "QID":"p1u2-d6",
       "type":"Pair",
       "question":"Au/nt",
       "correctAnswer":"Aunt"
     },
     {
       "QID":"p1u2-d7",
       "type":"Pair",
       "question":"Si/ster",
       "correctAnswer":"Sister"
     },
     {
       "QID":"p1u2-d9",
       "type":"Pair",
       "question":"Tw/ins",
       "correctAnswer":"Twins"
     },
     {
       "QID":"p1u2-d10",
       "type":"Pair",
       "question":"Child/ren",
       "correctAnswer":"Children"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c1",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Sch/ool /Bag",
      "correctAnswer":"School Bag"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c2",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Bo/ok",
      "correctAnswer":"Book"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c3",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"P/en",
      "correctAnswer":"Pen"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c4",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Era/ser",
      "correctAnswer":"Eraser"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c5",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Pen/cil",
      "correctAnswer":"Pencil"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c6",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Ca/se",
      "correctAnswer":"Case"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c7",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Rul/er",
      "correctAnswer":"Ruler"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c8",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Cray/ons",
      "correctAnswer":"Crayons"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c9",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Gl/ue",
      "correctAnswer":"Glue"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c10",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Stap/ler",
      "correctAnswer":"Stapler"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c11",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Scis/sors",
      "correctAnswer":"Scissors"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c12",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Note/book",
      "correctAnswer":"Notebook"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c13",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Pa/per",
      "correctAnswer":"Paper"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c14",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Bot/tle",
      "correctAnswer":"Bottle"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c15",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Lunch/box",
      "correctAnswer":"Lunchbox"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c16",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Sn/acks",
      "correctAnswer":"Snacks"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c17",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Home/work",
      "correctAnswer":"Homework"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c18",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Fol/der",
      "correctAnswer":"Folder"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c19",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"Sharp/ener",
      "correctAnswer":"Sharpener"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p1u3-c20",
      "type":"Picture",
      "question":"High/light/er",
      "correctAnswer":"Highlighter"
     }
   ]
}
